Hello friends, my name is Anil Rajpurohit
and today I am presenting to you
ICC Prudential Life Insurance
launched a new product on 21st June 2023, which is called
Protest in Game. As you
can understand from the name, we are talking about products i.e. term
insurance and we are
talking about profit in game i.e. equity. So, there is a
plan where
you will get equity based return and also
insurance tax up to 100 times of your premium, you will also get
income tax benefit
and you will
also get liquidity under Parcel Viral. So to know this complete plan,
you should watch this video of mine completely
and if you like the video then join my YouTube channel
Anil Rajput X
Karna Na Bhole. Thank you.
Now before I tell you all the features of the product,
I want to show you some such
scenario of India that
why this product has been launched, what are
its objectives. So according to a survey,
one person dies every minute in India.
Here about 4 lakh people die
and about 7.45 people are forgotten in their entire
life.  If
a person dies due to some reason, then here, if we
talk about insurance, then definitely the
risk of death will be discussed in the context of that. So, the risk of death
in a person's life is that
due to that his family can suffer a lot of
financial loss. So,
what risk can this pose in a person's life, either he may die a
natural death early
or he may die in an accident early
or he had an accident but did not die
but became disabled forever, so
how can he do this in such a situation, for the production of his family,
for the financial security of his family
and if the customer does not get anything then he will survive.
Natural early death is neither accident nor
disability, so
he wants that when he retires, when he is
ahead of his time, he should get a huge amount
so that he can enjoy his retirement.
Keeping all these things in mind, the product has been designed for you.
Now let us understand the three main features of this policy.
First, you will get your annual
premium.  You will get up to 100 times the insurance amount, that
is, if your premium is
one lakh rupees, then you will get insurance tax up to 1 crore.
Secondly, you will
also get accidental death tax. You can also take
accidental death tax of one crore against ₹1 crore, that is, if there is
death in an accident, then you will get ₹2 crore, if there is
natural death, then you will get ₹1 crore. The
third feature is permanent disability.
Many times a person does not die in an accident
but he becomes disabled, so in
this date you will get ₹1 crore anyway. So
these are the three major features of this policy.
Now, what are the requirements from the customer to take this policy? It has been
simplified a lot.
You do
not need to provide income proof here. You
can declare your income when the agent
comes to meet you or when you make an online purchase.
If you have a minimum income of ₹300,000 in the proposal form, then you are eligible to take this policy.
Secondly, even if you are
12th pass, this policy  Now you
can purchase. In this plan,
even those who have passed 12th standard are getting benefits in computer products, but even if you are
12th pass, you can take this policy
without giving income proof and
you can get a video medical test done till 45 years onwards. If
you do not want to get a physical medical test done then it will be fine,
but if you had done it after 45 years and above,
you will also have to undergo a physical medical test. So there are
three things, there is no retirement without income proof, if you are
12th pass then it will be fine and
your medical test will be a video medical test if you have one
till 45 years.
Now, because this is a market based plan, it is an
equity based plan, it is a ULIP plan, so there are
charges in it, but the
good thing about this policy is that these charges are returned to you.
Whatever charges you make,
double of that, sometimes even triple of that,
your charges are returned to you. For example, the
mortality charge which is deducted
in your policy, it will be returned to you after doubling it from the 11th year onwards
and after the 25th year, you will get it
back three times. Secondly, you will get
back the premium location charge, double of that.  It will
go and one of the biggest unique features
which no other company in the industry has
yet is that this feature is not there in this type
of policy where you
get maturity booster. Maturity booster
means that when your policy is about to mature,
suppose you have purchased the policy for 30
years, or purchase it for 40 years, then
when the policy term is about to expire, then
its last two years i.e. last eight
quarters will be
added, so this will be a huge amount
which you will get on maturity.
Now let's talk about the basic features of this policy.
Minimum insurance tax:
To buy this policy, you will have to take ₹50 lakhs.
Maximum you can take insurance up to ₹1 crore.
This is a little
story, I felt that the
option of more than six months should have been kept open
because some companies which are competitors
in the market sometimes charge more than ₹1 crore.
If we look at the premium payment in this type of policy, then
five years, six years, seven years, eight years and 10
This is available in Air 12 Air Limited and
you can also select Regular Pay. A person from 18 years to 7
years can take the policy and
this policy should mature till the maximum age of 85. If we
talk about this policy
because it is equity based, you will
get 18 funds to invest and
you will also get some investment status, so
now according to your retirement, you
can select any of the 18 funds as per your choice, you
can also do switching, if
after 5 years you have to retire with
some money then you can take up to 20% of your fund value,
but for example, if your
fund value is 10 lakhs and if you need ₹200000 at home, then
in this policy you can withdraw ₹2 lakhs without any bond,
in this you will get another facility called
system,
after 5 years, if you want that every year
or every month you can select that
I should get a certain portion in my account every year, by using the
system you can take
10% of your fund value.  If you have a fund value of Rs. 1 lakh and you have
decided yearly that 6% of your fund value should be
deposited in your account, then
Rs. 60,000 every year will keep coming into your account, which is called systematic withdrawal. Once it is fixed, Rs. 60,000 will keep coming to your account. Your
final policy revival is done, then you
can revive this policy for 3 years. If due to
any reason you do not pay the premium on time, then
within 3 years you
can revive the policy by paying the remaining premium of this policy. You will get the benefit of income tax. You get a
separate limit of Rs. 250,000. Apart from savings, you
also get the benefit that
if you feel that you want to cancel the policy within 15 days of purchasing the policy, then
you
can get the premium paid on your policy back by cancelling it.
Loan is not available in this policy.
So now let us understand this product
with illustration. Here I have
taken an example, he is a 35 year old male
and here he is for 10 years.  You are
taking premium payment and
paying for the policy term of 40 years. You are
taking natural tax of Rs 1 crore, there is
accident date benefit of Rs 1 crore and you are
purchasing disability tax of Rs 1 crore.
For this, you will have to pay a premium of Rs 125,000,
which also includes your rider premium. The
premium without rider will be Rs 1 lakh. So,
now
I will try to explain to you exactly how this works.
Here you will see that the
customer has paid Rs 1 lakh without rider.
This is the premium of Indian. Here their
location charges etc. are being paid,
mortality charges are being paid, which you get
back doubled.
If you notice here, just like you get your mortality tax
back, in this way
you get back this charge doubled and after 25 years you get
back 3 times.
Secondly, you will see in this policy which has a
huge impact, its
name is
Maturity Booster. This site is not in any company,
what happens is that in the last eight
quarters
You used to get 20% of the average fund value of eight quarters
here. Here you will see that you
get Rs 13 lakh 65 thousand, which is
probably not available in other companies right now. Because of this,
if you notice here, its
fan value is Rs
8741000, Rs 8700000. If you
compare it with its competitors, then it will be Rs
47 instead of Rs 87.
I will also show you the video of the competitors, how it
works. So what is the benefit for the customer here
that they
also have natural calamity insurance of Rs 1 crore. If there is an
accidental death of Rs 1 crore, then Rs
2 crore will be received. Even if there is
no death in the accident but there is disability,
Rs 1 crore is received. Even if nothing happens,
you will see that you are getting Rs 87 lakh.
This is at 8%, whereas the average return in the Indian market is 15
to 16% since 1979. So
here  But they can also get higher returns. Along with
this,
you also get tax benefit on investment up to 1.25 rupees
in ATC and the maturity is
also tax free and if you
want to withdraw money from it after 5 years, then you
can withdraw money or
you will get multiple facilities in parcel. Now if
I present these competitors in front of you,
where instead of one lakh rupees, the
premium is getting reduced by about 9000 here,
if you notice, it is going to be 91000.
Here also you get the charges doubled and you get them
back.
Okay, you will see here that by
finding the charger addition, you
start getting it back here but here you do
not get it by doing this maturity booster
and if you notice here
and
see how much is being paid here
whereas how much is being paid there, if you see a
difference then you should compare it, compare it
before purchasing any policy and
who is the best person for you to compare.
9909403412 on this tomorrow  I will definitely do it, thank you. If we
talk about the Fauji policy, is it
necessary to be 12th pass in it? Yes, it is necessary to be 12th
pass or have 10th plus diploma.
Secondly, if a customer meets with an
accident and becomes disabled, then he will get
disability support in the form of
insurance tax of Rs. 1 crore and if he
dies after a few years, then he will
also get the natural insurance tax of Rs. 1 crore, that is, he will
also get the benefit of disability tax and the normal
insurance tax, he will also get both. If we
talk about parcel withdrawal, then
you can take 20% of your fund value through
partial withdrawal after 5 years. Let us talk about what will be the difference in parcel withdrawal,
then there will be no difference in it,
your insurance tax will remain the same,
yes, there will definitely be a difference on your maturity,
if you have withdrawn the money, then its impact,
if you survive on this date, will it
come on your maturity, but if you die, then you will
get the higher of the fund value, so finally  If I
summarize it, it's a good product. It's a
very good product where you get
good insurance coverage and
good returns. As you've
seen in the comparison, you see a
significant difference in fund value compared to competitors. You
get 87 stocks compared to 47, you get a maturity booster, which other
companies don't have. You get
income tax benefits.
You can also withdraw money under liquidity by parcel withdrawal. You have
18 funds available for investment. You have a
lot of investment opportunities. So,
this is a very good product
and a very good company. It's a leading company. The
company's claim settlement ratio is also very
good. The front-end
performance of ULIP is also very good, which
you
can check on the internet or by visiting the website. From the different funds available,
you can invest in the fund according to your needs.
For more information or to
purchase a policy, you can contact me.
Anil Rajpurohit is my mobile number.
9909403412 You can WhatsApp me your need on this number.
Follow and share. Thank you so much.